http://www.christmaswishlist.net/support/privacy.asp

14 Days Remaining 'til Christmas!
Currently serving 37,282 users and 211,842 wish list items!
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage,
our support page, and at other points where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the My Christmas Wish List website. We
collect information from you when you register on our site, or when you make updates to personal information
within your profile. The types of personal information collected on these pages are: name and email address. We
do not collect any sensitive financial or identity information such as credit/debit card information, social
security numbers, physical address, driver's license number, etc.
Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the
"do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
The Way We Use Information
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
This is what makes it possible to have your own profile and wish list.
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
To answer the email we receive using the return email addresses. Such addresses are not used for any
other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
To use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with
advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on
our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
To send periodic emails including, but not limited to, login and password retrieval, messages from other
users in your group(s), and news, updates, or reminders about the site itself.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways
unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise
prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied personal information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then
stored in our Database only to be accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
We do not store any sensitive information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) on our servers.
Our Use of Cookies
Yes, we do make use of cookies to enable certain features of the site. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information,
such as whether you are logged into the site or not.
We may also use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Disclosure of Information to Outside Parties
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third Party Links
At our discretion, we may include links to third party sites, products, or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their profile, going to the 'My Profile' page, and clicking on the Edit link next to the Personal Information section.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act).
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on November 4, 2008.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
www.christmaswishlist.net1252 Okeechobee RoadWest Palm Beach, FL 33401USA
